Guide to the Herbert Brodkin Television Production Files
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Playhouse 90, 1958-60
  - Production files, 1958-60 (Box 29, Folder 624-626)
    "Shadows Tremble" by Earnest Kinoy
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 627)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 628)
    "The Blue Men" by Alvin Boretz
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 629)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 630)
    "The Velvet Alley" by Rod Serling
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 631)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 632)
    "A Quiet Game Of Cards" by Reginald Rose
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 633)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 634)
    "Child Of Our Time" by Michel del Castillo
  - Scripts (Volume 6), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 635)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 636)
    "The Second Man" by Edward Grierson
  - Scripts (Volume 7), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 637)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 638)
    "The Raider" by Loring Mandel
  - Scripts (Volume 8), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 639)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 640)
    "Made In Japan" by Joseph Stefano
  - Scripts (Volume 9), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 641)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 642)
    "A Trip To Paradise" by Adrian Spies
  - Scripts (Volume 10), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 643)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 644)
    "In Lonely Expectation" by Mayo Simon
  - Scripts (Volume 11), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 645)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 30, Folder 646)
    "The Day Before Atlanta" by John Gay
  - Scripts (Volume 12), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 647)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 30, Folder 648)
    "Judgment At Nuremberg" by Abby Mann
  - Scripts (Volume 13), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 649)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 30, Folder 650)
    "Diary Of A Nurse" by Arthur Hailey
  - Scripts (Volume 14), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 651)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 30, Folder 652)
    "Marriage Of Strangers" by Reginald Rose
  - Scripts (Volume 15), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 653)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 30, Folder 654)
    "Out Of Dust" by John Gay
  - Scripts (Volume 16), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 655)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 30, Folder 656)
    "The Rank And File" by Rod Serling
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 657)
  - Production files, 1959 Dec (Box 30, Folder 658)
    "The Silver Whistle" by Robert McEnroe
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 659)
  - Production files, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 660)
    "To The Sound Of Trumpets" by John Gay
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 661)
  - Production files, 1960 Feb (Box 30, Folder 662)
    "The Cruel Day" by Reginald Rose
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 663)
  - Production files, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 664)
    "Tomorrow" by Horton Foote
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1960 (Box 31, Folder 665)
  - Production files, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 666)
    "The Hiding Place" by Adrian Spies
- Sebastian, 1966-67
  - Scripts, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 667)
  - Production Files, 1966-67 (Box 31, Folder 668-672)
- Shane, 1966
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 673)
  - Production files, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 674-679)
    The Distant Bell
    The Bitter, The Lonely
    The Wild Geese
    Poor Tom's A-Cold
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 680)
  - Production files, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 681-684)
    The Hant
    The Other Image
    An Echo Of Anger
    Killer In The Valley
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 685)
  - Production files, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 686-688)
    Day Of The Hawk
    Blue Organdy
    The Day The Wolf Laughed
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 689)
  - Production files, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 690-692)
    The Silent Gift
    The Big Fifty
    A Long Night Of Mourning
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1966 (Box 32, Folder 693)
  - Production files, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 694-695)
    The Great Invasion
    A Man-d Be Proud